The world.
What a glorious place.
Seek freedom, and it will lie
stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides
your restless spirit,
seize it, raise your flag, and stand tall.
I think back to the time
when my search first began.
I left behind those shores of sand.
For the endless everlasting
world out there.
I know that with the
burning passion driving me.
Someday, somewhere, I'll finally see the
light I have searched for everywhere?.
When the summer sun is shining.
Shaking the sails of my heart. I know.
A brand new world that has been hiding.
Has opened up its doors for me to go.
A way from the moon's sky.
Wearing in the troubled waves.
From all despair I can be saved.
For the horizon on the other side is.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Is what I am for.
And though I travel far
from where my search began.
Over seas of green and shores of sand.
Through the endless
everlasting world I bear.
I know that with this
burning passion driving me.
Some days somewhere I'll finally see
the light I will search for everywhere.?
You got something you want to
say to me, you little brat?
Well, speak up! I do.
Give back Pop's gold, every bit of it.
What gold?
You mean the junk we got
from Old Man Cricket?
Maybe it's news to you but
that's what pirates do.
Ever heard of looting?
But what am I saying?
You're just a pathetic
dreamer who can't open his
eyes long enough to get a
good look at the real world.
Well then, if stealing is what we pirates
do, I guess I should steal the gold.
Back then?
That's cute but be serious.
Can you really fight?
I mean, do you even know
how to throw a punch?
I saw your fighting skills earlier.
You're very good at.
Just standing there! Huh?
I was right.
That's him.
You're still hanging on to
that thing, didn't you hear?
It's worthless.
Get rid of it.
But if this is the real thing,
then Bellamy's in trouble.
He's good,
but you have to admit he can't beat someone
with a hundred million berry bounty.
You've got to be joking.
Look at him.
He's just a little runt.
He's probably not even worth the
trouble it would take to fight him.
Just seeing him now makes me doubt
that thirty million berry bounty.
Standing there, is he
going to get the gold back?
What?
You freezing up like this afternoon?
Admit it, you're too scared to fight me!
This afternoon was
different, I'm not scared.
We'll see about that real soon, Straw Hat!
I'm sick of listening to you, so I think
I'll shut you up for good this time!
It's collapsing!
Don't worry, this won't take long!
Spring Sniper!
You're nothing but a little boy
who still believes in dreams.
You disgraced the rest of us
by calling yourself a pirate.
It's time to stop this
foolish dreaming and grow up.
Now let's end this.
He did it right for it. Run!
Looks like your dreams are at an end.
He's alive!
You don't know when to quit, do you?
Fine, have it your way!
We're just getting to the good part!
Spring!
Power!
Bellamy disappeared!
This is the same kind of
move he pulled to beat Race!
So you want the gold back, huh?
Because old man crickets
your friend wake up
he's nothing but a decrepit
fool who spends all
his time chasing after
a 400 year old lie but
that's probably what you
like about him right you
like to call yourselves
pirates but you know
nothing there's no city
of gold little island in
the sky just oceans and
ships and the men who
sail them you asked if i
know how to throw a punch
just finish him so we can drink bellamy
watching you beat him
since this made me thirsty
So long, Straw Hat!
Hey, quit messing around,
Bellamy, and get up.
The joke's over.
We know that runt couldn't beat you.
Come on, get up!
This really isn't funny anymore.
Now snap out of it!
You have to get up and
show that kid who you are.
You're a real pirate, not like him.
Your bounty's up to 55 million.
You can't lose to some rookie!
Those two together are worth $160 million!
The bounties are higher
than yours, Malami.
Know what that means?
You're dead meat!
You see now?
I told you it was true.
And now Cricket's gold.
Give it back.
Fix the ship, monkey crew, fix the ship.
Bang the nails, monkey
crew, bang the nails.
Saw the wood, monkey crew, saw the wood.
Wow, these guys must be pretty tough.
They were just beaten unconscious
and now they're here fixing the ship.
Either they're the world's fastest healers
or Choppers, the world's best doctor.
Why didn't you go with Luffy? What?
What's with you?
Fight, don't fight.
Go, don't go. Do this. No, do that.
Make up your mind already.
You're scared.
Those guys beat you the first time around.
That's what you think?
You don't get it.
They didn't beat us.
Refusing to fight doesn't
mean that we were afraid.
When there's no reason to fight, the
only way to win is to stand down.
Oh, I see. Stand down. Real brave.
You don't know anything about fighting.
Just shut up.
Don't tell me to shut up.
Like it matters.
You never listen anyway.
I know more about fighting
than you ever will.
Be careful!
Yeah, be more careful with the ship!
We're trying to fix the
ship, not destroy it!
You're nothing but a thief!
At least I'm not a coward!
That wasn't too hard to find.
It's not possible.
How could we lose?
Hey, you! Come back here! You hear me?
You stupid runt!
I'm talking to you!
I'll get him!
We won't be beaten by some pretend pirate!
I'll show you a real punch!
Where are you going?
Where am I going?
Up there!
Captain? Captain!
What? Is...
is this really the place?
The legendary cave where
Captain John hid his treasure?
The treasure he killed
so many innocents to get?
Yes, that's right.
Now look alive, boys.
The treasure is near, but
so is unspeakable danger.
If you let your guard down, even for a
second, then death will creep up on you.
There's no telling what
kind of monsters will appear
or what vicious booby
traps await to kill us all
Come on men another fine day of
carving out tunnels awaits us.
Oh
You must be the new guys they sent down.
Right boss all the man really needs is a
pickaxe in his hand in a tunnel to dig.
You can say that again.
A hard day's work is a wonderful thing,
and because of our good
old-fashioned elbow grease,
everyone who comes to
this tunnel will smile.
It's liberating!
You know, after all this hard labor,
we ought to head over to
the old bilge barge for a...
How dare you make me work
like one of your lackeys!
Not one single piece of
treasure on that whole
rotten island you know
you should really watch!
What you say, Moji?
If there's one thing the
captain hates, it's being wrong.
I mean, can't you see how red he's
gotten with all the embarrassments?
Whose nose is a big red embarrassment?
I hate to interrupt, but we
do not have time for this.
What are we going to do
about those Straw Hats?
They are quickly becoming the new
favorite pirates in the Grand Line.
I have a plan, of course, you moron.
We let them go on their merry way.
What? Why?
Well, you see, before an evil witch
feasts upon the flesh of children,
the first thing she does is
make sure to fatten them up.
Understand me?
Idiots, this is why I'm captain, see the
bigger the bounty gets on the Straw Hats!
I see, you're a genius captain,
that way when you take them down the
bounty on your head will get even higher?
Yes exactly,
you're amazing captain, shall we throw
a party in honor of your brilliance?
Oh why not
Is this really the time
to be throwing a party?
After all,
how can you plan on beating
Luffy in the Straw Hats
when you're having the faintest
idea of where they are?
Don't be such a party before Alvida.
We'll find Luffy when we find him, okay?
If you're looking for Luffy,
I can tell you where he is.
Ha!
You see, this guy over here is
going to tell us where he is.
Problem solved!
Hey, hold on!
Who are you?
Sorry for crashing your party,
but I simply couldn't resist the
delicious aromas of your feast.
My name is Porkus D.
Ace, but you can call me Ace.
Oh, no need to be so formal.
Nice to meet you, too.
I mean, what are you
doing here, you idiot?
I couldn't care less about
what your name is, Mr.
Porkus D. Ace. Oh, Captain.
Captain, this guy is...
She's the Fire Fist.
Fire Fist Ace.
Captain of the White
Beard Pirates second unit.
Not White Beards.
Ah, so you know the old man.
What a nice...
He fell asleep?
No, I won't. Why not?
Captain, this could be our only chance.
If we can take out Firefist Ace of the
Whitebeard Pirates, we'll be famous.
I said no!
Remember this, men, and remember it good.
This is the most important
lesson you'll ever learn.
Don't mess with the
Whitebeard Pirates. Ever!
Ha!
Whitebeard is a killer born and bred.
The only man who could go toe-to-toe
with Goldroger, the king of the pirates.
He is without a doubt the
strongest pirate alive and the
person closest to obtaining
the greatest treasure of all,
One Piece.
In other words, don't cross him!
Even if we were able to kill
Firefist Ace while he sleeps,
Whitebeard would avenge the murder of one
of his own with the
fury of a thunderstorm!
How is it that you know so much?
Pray tell.
well if you insist it was on the grand
line years ago i met that man face
to face and i've never been the same
since oh sorry about that i must have
goes off what the he's away hey why
the long faces everyone i thought this
was a party am i right oh yeah you're
right man commands having fun again
Ace, you sure know how
to have a good time!
Whoa, you guys got a lion?
Be a good kitty and jump through
that flaming hoop on two legs!
Come on, Rich, show him your stuff!
Red Hair and White Beard?
Yes, Red Hair made contact.
That is disturbing.
I assume he didn't go himself.
No, he sent one of his crew.
Elder, I'm concerned.
These two working together could
mean real trouble for the rest of us.
Yes, but let's wait for now.
They haven't done anything yet,
and Red Hair isn't the type
to act unless he's provoked.
We'll keep an eye on them, but I'm afraid
we have more pressing worries to tend to.
We need to focus on the seven warlords.
With Crocodile gone, we are
in need of a replacement.
Pirates they may be.
The warlords keep things balanced.
With one of their number gone, we
may encounter serious problems.
What plans have we made so far? Sir,
we've called all of the warlords
to Mariegeois for a meeting,
but there's no way to know how
many of them will actually show up.
They are pirates, after all.
They do as they please.
Dammit, crocodile.
It's because of you
that we're in this mess.
We can't let the pirates that
defeated him go unpunished.
We have to retaliate swiftly.
I want all of our energy concentrated
on finding this Monkey D. Luffy.
Navy headquarters, Marie Joie.
Announcing the arrival of warlords Don
Quixote Doflamingo and Bartholomew Puma.
What the hey stop it what are you doing
it's not me i don't know what's going on?
This isn't the time for
your stupid press it's
no break it's like
something's moving my hands!
And i can't stop them
that's ridiculous i can't
breathe stop it what the
devil are you fools doing?
Are you trying to kill me
i told you it's not me.
Get off of me for themselves.
Stop it!
Get off of me!
This is your doing!
Do you find this entertaining, Doflamingo?
Yes, actually.
But if you don't mind,
I'd like to get this little shindig
started sometime in the near future.
Unless you haven't had enough.
You idiot!
What do you think you're doing now?
This foolishness has gone
on long enough, Doflamingo!
Stop! Enough!
There's no time for this.
Now sit down.
There are pressing matters to discuss.
I apologize for the late welcome.
Thank you for coming, scum of the sea.
Thank you.
So thoughtful of you using
my formal title like that.
Let's begin.
I doubt any more of the
Warlord's plan to attend.
Truth be told, two out of six is
more than I expected. Smart man.
I didn't plan to come either,
but the business back home's going
so well, it practically runs itself.
So I took a vacation.
Ended up here out of sheer boredom.
Forgive me for not applauding
your business success.
I'm afraid that for the rest of us,
there are few things more distressing
than a booming pirate industry.
While I admire a man who's
not afraid to speak his mind,
I would remember, Admiral,
that there are limits.
So good to hear your dulcet
tones again, Dolph Lamingo.
And you, Admiral Sengoku, I
hope you've been well. Hawkeye!
I must say,
I've never understood why
the seven warlords and
the marines insist on
pretending they get along,
but perhaps you can enlighten me.
Hawkeye Mihawk, perhaps this little
get-together will be interesting after all.
What brings you here, Mihawk?
Well, I heard about your meeting
and thought I might sit in on it.
I have an interest in the
pirates you'll be discussing,
and I'd like to stay informed.
That is all.
Forgive the intrusion,
but if Hawkeye's staying,
perhaps you won't mind
adding one more to the party.
I will tell you, though, my intentions
are a bit less passive than his are.
Who are you exactly?
And how'd you get in here anyway?
Quite a prestigious group
you've assembled here, Admiral.
I'm truly impressed.
I was hoping I might join you.
I heard the news about Crocodile.
It's a terrible shame he's gone.
Fortunately for you, I've come here to
offer a solution to your little problem.
The six warlords just doesn't
have the same ring to it, does it?
i know him that man's lafitte
who's lafitte aha someone
here has heard my name before
i'd have thought it had
been forgotten a long time
ago he was a respected peace
officer in the west blue sea
he disappeared after a scandal
ruined his reputation glad to
see you're so well informed
who i am doesn't matter
all that's in the past i've
come here to talk to you
about another man one who i
believe would make an excellent
addition to the warlords
shanks i haven't heard that name
in a long time so after all these
years he sent me a letter yeah and
whatever it says must be important or
else he wouldn't have chosen me to
deliver it for him i see you're high
up on the food chain are you well
uh not exactly i mean i am still new
to the red-haired pirates but it's
not like it's my first pirate gig
i've been around for a while and
i'm pretty sure i've made a name for
myself hey you guys have heard about
that famous pirate named rostar
right uh-uh i've never heard of him
before so i know what were you saying
hey what are you he sent me a
letter when did that kid become so
important that he thought it it
would be okay to send me a letter.
Time to take him down
a notch. Wait, hold on.
What do you think you're doing?
That was an important letter.
This is Shakes you're dealing with,
the leader of the Red-Haired Pirates.
You forget I'm Captain Whitebeard.
Captain, it's time for
your medicine again.
I've got all the medicine
I need right here.
Now silence, fetch me another keg.
I hope you know my boss
will hear about all of this.
Don't make me laugh.
Anyway, I already have a pretty good
idea of what the letter's about.
He's worried about
Blackbeard and that kid Ace.
Tell Shanks that if he wants to
talk, he can come see me himself.
Now why don't you take off?
I'm too busy to talk
to a snot-nosed rookie.
Run home to your boss.
The old man hasn't changed a bit.
How are you laughing at this, boss?
I figured that would happen.
Don't worry about it.
Just give me a little bit more time.
I promise I can straighten this guy out.
I don't know what you plan to do,
my friend, but forget about it.
You did a good job.
Now just get yourself
back to base, all right?
But what about my pride?
I have to show this guy who I am!
Hey, your life is more
important to me than your pride.
Come on, there's nothing
more for you to do out there.
We have some things to plan.
So, what are we gonna do, Vice?
We're going.
Prepare to set sail, men!
You're going to see Whitebeard?
Sure am.
Even you can't think the government won't
react if you pull a stunt like that.
No, Beckman, I fully expect them to.
I just don't care. Huh?
Now's not the time to
worry about the government.
Before much longer, they'll
be the ones worrying about us.
You heard him, man!
Let's get going!
All right, boys.
Let's get some grog ready to take with us.
Teach.
That's right.
He's the captain of the
pirate crew to which I belong.
Tell me, if I've never heard
of him, what use is he to me?
With no reputation, he
would pose no threat.
You know, I thought you
might feel that way.
And I assure you, we need
only a little bit more time.
We are drawing up a plan at the moment
that should take care of everything.
Well, he's caught my interest anyway.
Why don't we give him a try, Admiral?
The crew I belong to is known
as the Blackbeard Pirates.
I suggest that you remember that name.
Hey, did you hear?
Someone beat up Bellamy earlier.
What?
Who could do that?
This kid looked too bright-eyed to be
even worth 30 million, but 100 million.
So what's our next move, Captain?
The kid just got lucky.
He's not really worth that much.
Why don't you throw that
away before I do it for you?
That's a net body, you!
Well, that ought to shut him up.
I was looking for someone with
a bounty that was worth my time.
The crew's going to be rich soon, boys.
Very stinking rich.
That's what I wanted to hear.
It's about time we all
had full pockets again.
Hey, Captain.
Weren't we meeting up
with Lafitte in Mocktown?
I haven't seen him around anywhere.
Guess we'll just have
to leave without him.
We can't let a bounty like that get away.
Am I right, Ogre?
Good idea.
We gotta do all the
living we can right now.
It comes for everyone,
sometimes even pirates.